- He's got Amy now.
- Yeah, he does...
(Penny:)...but it's not the same.
- Why?
(Leonard:)Um...
Well, all right, you know how
in Harry Potter and the Half-Blood Prince...
(Penny:)...Ron didn't abandon Harry
because Harry started dating Ron's sister?
(Leonard:)Harry and Ginny get together?
(Penny:)Sorry, spoiler alert. My point is,
as much as I want to live with you...
(Penny:)...I can't do it knowing how much
Sheldon needs you.
(Leonard:)Please. The only thing he needs me for
is to be his whipping boy.
(Leonard:)His stooge, his doormat.
(Penny:)Well, you know what they say,
if it ain't broke...
(Leonard:)Wow, it sounds to me like
you don't want us to live together.
(Penny:)No. No, no, I do. I do.
It's just... It's a really big step.
(Leonard:)Is it? We're together all the time.
Financially, it makes great sense.
(Leonard:)Can you think of one reason
why we shouldn't do this?
(Penny:)Well, um...